!Azov ransomware!

Hello, my name is hasherezade.
I am the polish security expert.

To recover your files contact us in twitter:
@hasherezade
@VK_Intel
@demonslay335
@malwrhunterteam
@LawrenceAbrams
@bleepincomputer

Слава Україні! #Всебудеукраїна

[Why did you do this to my files?]
I had to do this to bring your attention to the problem.
Do not be so ignorant as we were ignoring Crimea seizure for years.

The reason the west doesn't help enough Ukraine.
Their only help is weapons, but no movements towards the peace!
Stop the war, go to the streets!
Since when that Z-army will be near to my Polska country.
The only outcome is nuclear war.
Change the future now!
Help Ukraine, come to the streets!
We want our children to live in the peaceful world.

#ВсебудеУкраїна

--------------------------------------------------

Biden doesn't want help Ukraine.
You people of United States, come to the streets, make revolution!
Keep America great!
--------------------------------------------------

Germany plays against their own people!
Du! Ein mann aus Deutschland, komm doch, komm raus!
Das ist aber eine Katastrophe, was Biden zu ihnen gemacht hat.
Wie war das schoen, wenn Merkel war da?
---------------------------------------------------

#TaiwanIsChina